<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyle&#39;s new world</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://kylewen.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kylewen.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2014 21:50:26 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2014 21:50:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>使用Jekyll和Git創建這個網站</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;如果你對編程有所了解，就一定聽說過&lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com&quot; title=&quot;Github&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;它號稱是程序員的facebook，有著很高的人氣。 但是如果你很幸運不是一個程序員，或者你是一個不用煩惱這些亂七八糟的程序員，那麼相信我，你一樣可以創建一個跟我一模一樣的個人站點。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;技術很簡單， 不用擔心&lt;/strong&gt;
從整個建站到完成，大致涉及到以下的服務和技術:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;在&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.godaddy.com/&quot;&gt;Godaddy&lt;/a&gt;上註冊你喜歡的域名，然後將你域名託管給(域名解釋）&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dnspod.cn/&quot;&gt;DNSPod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;將你的代碼託管在&lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com&quot; title=&quot;Github&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;，最後使用&lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;發佈你的個人網站&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;下載使用Jekyll，編寫整個網站&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;如果你希望你的網站有評論功能，可以使用Disqus託管評論&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;除了域名购买需要花点银两，剩下的服务全部免费。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;购买绑定个性域名&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;直奔Godaddy，注册邮箱验证这些常规手续就不说了。然后在搜索框中输入自己想要的域名，点击查看是否可以注册。当你选定域名后，进入付款环节，系统会提供一些需要额外付费的推荐服务，比如隐私保护，域名邮箱，网站空间等，不想买就不用管，结账！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;虽然Godaddy家也提供域名解析服务，毕竟是国外的服务器，出于对可能被墙的而导致域名无法访问的担忧，还是把域名解析服务迁移到国内比较稳定的服务商处。不用担心，这个过程不会对你的域名所有权产生任何影响。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DNSPod家的服务很好用，而且免费，整个过程简单到没有给我留下任何可折腾的空间。 官方的帮助文档已经有了很详实的介绍，包括godaddy注册的域名如何使用DNSPod,只需三步即可。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;不过由于我们接下来会使用Github Pages来发布网站，因此需要额外插入一步： 在DNSPod自己的域名下添加两条A记录(或者修改原有存在的那条A记录并添加一条)，地址分别为：23.235.39.133和(一樣) 23.235.39.133，正是Github Pages的服务IP地址。最终效果如下：
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/Dnspod.png&quot; alt=&quot;pod&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;域名的配置部分完成，需耐心等待解析生效。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;github-pages&quot;&gt;使用Github Pages建立博客&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在此之前，你需要对Git和Github有基本的了解和掌握。这里有一份不错的&lt;a href=&quot;http://wulujia.com/2014/01/15/jekyll-github-blog/#toc_1&quot;&gt;基础教程&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylewen.com/2014/11/15/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylewen.com/2014/11/15/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why did I build this site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’t finally Friday I’m free again(what a busy week and it’s cold too). I believe the design of this site is almost done, at least, I am satisfied with the current outcome which basically uses Jekyll, Github and a little bit of HTML. Being honest, the invisible force that pushed me forward and had this site built was not something big but just the moment I realized my donmain name Kylewen.com was available in GoDaddy and only cost $10 dollar with promotion code for two years!! And then I just took out my credit card and purchased the domain name with no idea about what I was going to do about it at all.I really think the first moment I own my .com could be the my most exciting moment of the year. Thereafter my idea of building my own site is gradually strengthened and I just started it from ground up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of my life, I’ve embraced a number of hobbies: video games, sleeping, day dreaming, just to name a few. But none of them have changed the way I live, the way I think, the way I learn or have brough me as much as satifaction as building something on my own and sharing with others. I may be the only audience of this site but I will still keep working on it, Cuz I am happy of doing it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I write because&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t know&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What I think &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Until I read&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What I say&lt;/li&gt;
-Flannery O&#39;connor
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylewen.com/2014/11/13/%200%20to%20Blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylewen.com/2014/11/13/%200%20to%20Blog.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Blog like a Hacker</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the past two weeks and have been falling in love with &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com&quot; title=&quot;Github:social coding&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;. Git
is truly an amazing tool &amp;amp; so is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. I was going to say Version Control, but that ain’t fair, Git is so much more. You can create and publish Github pages online using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/what-are-github-pages/&quot; title=&quot;Automatic Page Generator&quot;&gt;Automatic Page Generator&lt;/a&gt;. If you prefer to work on your own, you can use github for Mac and Windows, or the Command line. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my next post, I will get into more details about how to create your own site by using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com&quot; title=&quot;Github:social coding&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-jekyll-and-why-do-i-care&quot;&gt;What’s Jekyll and Why do i Care?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware webiste generator. It requires a bit of ruby codes and transfers raw text files in various formats with &lt;a href=&quot;http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/syntax&quot; title=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;MarkDown&lt;/a&gt;, sort out files and then you are able to publish your favourite site to your favorite web serve. Jekyll also happens to be the engine behind GitHub Pages, which means !!!! you can use jekyll to create a project_folder (which contais all the required files for you site ) and push it to your own Github account ^repository^ (or github’s server) for free. Then You will write your post in a plain text file, run jekyll and push to your github server. sometimes, I still found myself getting lost as I tried to add some plugins to here or there for my site/blog but I was enjoying it. Moreover, every line of this site is mine, it turns out, that’s pretty important to me. Jekyll is cool, &amp;amp; I like cool stuffs. I started everything from scratch, and I don’t think i ended up with a particulary unique blog site. T.T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;if-i-can-do-it-you-can-do-it-&quot;&gt;If I can do it, you can do it. 世界這麼亂，裝純給誰看&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have distractions like I do such as Call Of Duty 11, League of Legend, movies, League of Lengend again, then trust me, you can build a blog/site better than this.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to go to the following sites and get the basic first:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://godaddy.com&quot; title=&quot;Godaddy&quot;&gt;GoDaddy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://dnspod.cn&quot; title=&quot;DNSPod&quot;&gt;DNSPod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com&quot; title=&quot;Github:social coding&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://disqus.com&quot; title=&quot;Disqus&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylewen.com/2014/11/08/How%20to%20Blog%20like%20a%20Hacker.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylewen.com/2014/11/08/How%20to%20Blog%20like%20a%20Hacker.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
